bostonproper.com 2019-02-01

# Sexy Dresses, Denim, Tops & Travel Clothes For Women | Boston Proper

Revision Date: May 31, 2018

We know that your privacy is important to you. It is important to us too. So, please read our privacy policy (the " **Privacy Policy** ").

If you voluntarily provide your personal information in the course of purchasing our products or using our services or website, we will take that as your agreement to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. However, we will respect your preferences as to whether and how you'd like us to communicate with you, and you may modify your preferences online or by contacting a Customer Service representative. ([Contact Us](https://www.bostonproper.com/FAQ/Customer_Service/Contact_Us/ "Contact Us"))

If you have registered to receive marketing communications from us and later change your mind, you may opt out of receiving direct marketing or promotional communications in electronic or printed form by writing or calling us at the [Contact Us](https://www.bostonproper.com/FAQ/Customer_Service/Contact_Us/ "Contact Us") information set out below, or by sending us an email with "unsubscribe" in the subject line to [customerservice@bostonproper.com](mailto:customerservice@bostonproper.com "customerservice@bostonproper.com").

If you opt out of receiving marketing information from us, we may still contact you concerning your specific transactions and communications with us.

## Information We May Collect

* * *

We may collect personal information, including your first and last name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, transaction information, credit or debit card information, birth month and day, content interests, cookies and usage data. We may collect this information when you:

  * make a purchase online or by phone;
  * save your information with us online or visit our site ([Cookies](https://www.bostonproper.com/faq/customer-service/privacy/#cookies));
  * opt in for emails or request catalogs or other marketing materials;
  * participate in a contest, sweepstakes, promotion or survey;
  * make inquiries concerning our merchandise or services;
  * participate in any geolocation services we offer (e.g., to inform you of new products and promotions that may be of interest to you.); and/or
  * are referred to us through a third-party marketing promotion.

To review or update personal information you've provided previously, sign in to our site and click "My Account." You may update stored information by clicking "Profile." Be sure to "Save" once you've completed your changes. You also may call or email Customer Service.

If you purchase merchandise or a gift card for another person, we also may collect personal information concerning the recipient in order to fulfill your request. We will assume that you have the recipient's permission to use his or her personal information for this limited purpose.

### How we may use the personal information we collect

We may use the personal information we collect to:

  * process, track and fulfill your order and contact you about the status of your order;
  * if you consent to join our mailing list, to
    * tell you about and administer our contests, sweepstakes and promotions;
    * send you emails, catalogs or other marketing materials about our merchandise or services; and
    * send you surveys about our merchandise or services;
  * offer you geolocation services (e.g., to inform you of new products and promotions that may be of interest to you.);
  * respond to your inquiries regarding our merchandise or services;
  * learn about your shopping preferences and improve your shopping experience;
  * help us address problems with and improve our site and our merchandise and services; and/or
  * protect the security and integrity of our site. We may also use your personal information in other ways for which we will provide notice and obtain your consent at the time of collection, to the extent required by law or this Privacy Policy.
  * communicate and send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, including marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you.

### How we may share the personal information we collect

We may share your personal information for the purposes described above in the following ways:

  * In the event of the sale or a merger of Boston Proper, information we have collected may be among the assets transferred.
  * We may share certain personal information with companies who provide certain services to us such as shipping, name and address verification, email distribution, and promotions management. We share only that information necessary for these companies to perform their requested services. Additionally, these companies are contractually obligated to protect this information and to use it for no other purpose. With co-sponsors of contests, sweepstakes or promotions.
  * With reputable companies whose products we believe may be of interest to you. We share only first and last names and mailing addresses but not email addresses.
  * With law enforcement upon request, as required by applicable law (such as by court order or subpoena), if necessary, in connection with a fraud investigation, or to protect and defend our customers' and our interests.

### Retention and storage of your personal information

We retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws.

## Cookies

* * *

Our site uses "cookies," which are small data files stored on your computer's hard drive or mobile device when you visit a site. Cookies may be used in a variety of ways to enhance and personalize your online browsing and shopping experience. For instance, cookies allow us to remember what's in your shopping cart, recognize you when you return to our site, track your orders, and monitor and maintain information about your visits. You may set your browser not to accept cookies ("do not track") or to notify you when you receive cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you will need to re-enter your personal information each time you decide to make a purchase online.

 **Examples of Cookies we use:**

  * Session Cookies: We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  * Preference Cookies: We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences, interest and various settings.
  * Security Cookies: We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

## Retention of Data

* * *

We will retain your Personal Data only for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

We will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when the data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our service and offering, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

## Third-Party Ads

* * *

We use a third-party provider to place our internet ads. The provider may collect anonymous information about your visits to our site and your interaction with our products and services. The provider may also use information about your visits to this and other sites to target advertisements for merchandise and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. The provider does not know your first and last name, address, phone number, email address or any of your other personally identifiable information. If you would like more information about this practice and your option to not have this anonymous information used by our third-party provider,[click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed "http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed").

## Security

* * *

We use various technologies and processes to help protect your information. Information such as your credit or debit card account number is transmitted through a secure server using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, absolute security can never be guaranteed.

We will never request your credit card or other personal information by email. If you receive an email that appears to be a request from us for personal information,  **Do Not Respond,**  as this may be a "phishing" scam designed to steal your information. Never include your credit or debit card number or other sensitive information in an email as it is not a secure means of transmitting information. We will only request such information during secure transactions on our site or through our Customer Service team.

It is your responsibility to safeguard any password you create to access "My Account" and to sign out when your visit is complete.

## Links to other websites

* * *

Our site may contain links to sites owned by third parties. Please review the privacy policy of any site you access through our site as we are not responsible for a third-party's privacy policy or practices.

### Children's privacy

Our site is not intended for use by children and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that information has been submitted by someone who is under the age of majority in your jurisdiction of residence, we will not use it. The child's parent or guardian should contact us if we have inadvertently collected such personal information and we will delete it from our files.

### International orders and users

For the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, we, one of our affiliates, or an unaffiliated service provider may process and store your personal information outside of your home country. Under the laws of those foreign countries, in certain circumstances courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies or security authorities in those foreign countries may be entitled to access your personal information.

If you reside or are located outside of the United States, please note that this site is hosted on our computer servers in the United States. Your use of this site or submission of personal information will constitute your consent to the transfer of personal information outside of your home country. 

## Policy changes

* * *

If our Privacy Policy changes, we will post the changes to our site with the date of revision. Your continued use of our site will constitute your agreement with our revised Privacy Policy. Please also note that our Privacy Policy is incorporated into our site's [Terms of Use](https://www.bostonproper.com/store/page.jsp?id=81809282 "Terms of Use"). 

## Updating and modifying your communication preferences

* * *

If you wish to update, delete or modify your personal information or do not wish to be contacted via email, direct mail and/or telephone, please make changes to "My Account" online or contact Customer Service. Provide your exact name and postal or email address so that we may identify you accurately. You may also "unsubscribe" from our email by using the link provided at the bottom of each email. If you ask us to remove you from marketing lists, we will maintain you on a "do not contact" list to ensure that we continue to honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your "do not email" request. It may take up to 8 weeks to process your "do not mail" request because mailings are planned long in advance. If you purchase online, we will continue to confirm your order and shipment status via email, postal address or telephone. If you change your mind about choices you've previously made, make changes to "My Account" online or contact Customer Service. ([Contact Us](https://www.bostonproper.com/FAQ/Customer_Service/Contact_Us/))

## Contact us

* * *

Boston Proper Customer Service   
1155 BROKEN SOUND PARKWAY NW SUITE A-D  
BOCA RATON, FL 33487

561.990.1700 

[customerservice@bostonproper.com  
](mailto:customerservice@bostonproper.com)
